[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMING IN PAIN]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TRUCK HORN BLARES]
[LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- Stop!
- [GUNSHOTS]
[FIREWORKS EXPLODING]
[METAL RODS CLANGING]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [BUS HORN HONKS]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[GUNSHOTS]
- [TRUCK HORN HONKS]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Where is what you promised me?
You said you'd find a way
to get your father surgery.
Where is it?! Where is it?!
I found work, Auntie.
I just need to locate someone,
then I'll get paid.
[THRILLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[MOTOR ENGINE REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[MOTOR ENGINE ROARS]
Are they really
going to help us?
Provide a lawyer
if we decide to sue the police?
But if we sue the cops...
it's like picking up a rock
and smashing it
against our own heads.
The patient's condition
is critical.
He needs surgery right away.
I'll find a way right now
to get my father
into surgery immediately.
Pa, please hold on tight.
I'm doing everything I can
so you'll get better soon.
I promise...
I won't let anything
happen to you, Pa.
Even if I have to risk
my very own life...
I won't let anything bad
befall you, Pa.
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
Stop pressuring Sam like that.
It's not helping her at all.
Sir, I'm not pressuring her,
she's just easily scared.
Maybe she's insecure?
I just want her to do better...
even if I don't trust her.
You question every
single thing Sam does.
She's actually very skilled.
Skilled?
Depends who you ask.
Excuse me, sir.
I have things to take care of.
[BROODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
Mr. Chan...
(In Cantonese) Happy New Year!
[MR. CHAN] Victor!
(In Cantonese) Wishing you
a prosperous New Year!
Mr. Chan, I'll see you later.
I have your gold.
See?
[MR. CHAN]
Good! Good!
Okay, Victor, I'll see you
later. Give me a call, okay?
Okay, I'll see you later.
[DOOR OPENS]
So Victor, are you meeting
with Mr. Chan now?
Yes, Pa.
We're meeting later.
But first,
I'm heading to Lao's wedding.
You'd put that ahead
of our business?
Lao's one of my people, Ma.
You have several deals
to finalize today.
That should be
your top priority.
Darling, let Victor be.
He knows what he's doing.
When we were just starting out,
we never wasted time
on trivial things like that.
That's what
you should inherit, Victor.
Mariano and I worked so hard
to build all of this.
So I want you
to prioritize the business.
This is for our family.
Yes, Ma.
Everything's all set
for tonight.
I've handled worse than this,
Ma.
Let's go.
[BRIEFCASES SNAPPING SHUT]
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[VICTOR] Lee.
Yes, boss?
Go to the Jade Imperial now.
If Mr. Chan gets there first,
take care of him, alright?
Sure, boss.
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
How was the thing
I asked you for?
Our flight to Malaysia
will be at midnight.
Everything's ready.
And me?
Where do you want me to go?
Attend the wedding with me.
Just stick close to me
the whole evening, got it?
- [ENGINES REVVING]
- [INTENSE ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[FESTIVAL INSTRUMENTS PLAYING]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[INTENSE ROCK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FESTIVAL INSTRUMENTS
PLAYING CONTINUES]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[INTENSE ROCK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[METAL CLANGING]
[FESTIVAL INSTRUMENTS
PLAYING CONTINUES]
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE REVVING]
- [WHISTLE BLOWS]
- You can't be here!
- [ENGINE ROARS]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[INTENSE ROCK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FESTIVAL INSTRUMENT
PLAYING CONTINUES]
[PEOPLE CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
[BINOY] Even his height?
Is he tall? Short? What?
[TOLITS] I have no idea
what to do, man.
Gabo is asking
for the impossible here!
We're looking for someone
we haven't even met!
It's much easier to rob
and kidnap someone
than to look for someone
you haven't even met!
Hold it!
I thought you wanted
to turn over a new leaf?
And weren't you the ones
who insisted to join us?
We do want to turn over
a new leaf, Tekla.
Plus, if we don't join Gabo,
Mr. Paquito will be
on our case for sure!
He believes that we're
stabbing Gabo in the back!
Oh? What's the matter then?
Why are you all making a fuss?
We didn't force you
to come with us
but you keep on tagging along.
Alright, alright!
We'll join you guys.
We'll follow anything you say
even if it's to look for an ant!
Just let us join your group.
If you really want to become
a part of our group,
don't be picky!
Always heed Gabo's orders!
Exactly. And please,
can't you three just be grateful
that we gave you a job, huh?
It's supposed to be
just the four of us.
Now we have to split the money
with you too.
Let's move.
- Move!
- Let's go.
[IPE] Get a move on!
[BINOY] We're coming!
[BEEPS]
Alpha 1, onsite.
What's your status?
Alpha 2, in position.
Negative visuals on the target.
Status of the others?
[SEBASTIAN] All possible
locations covered.
Tiger isn't here yet.
Copy.
Maintain surveillance.
Copy that.
- [STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [FESTIVAL INSTRUMENTS PLAYING]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[FLAMES CRACKLING]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[UMALI] Deploy more police
in Chinatown.
We need to
maintain order there.
Especially today,
since it's Chinese New Year.
- Do you understand?
- [MEDINA] Yes, sir
[ESTRELLA] These are the reports
from the other night.
[MAX] You should run
those fingerprints already.
The Chief has been looking
for that for so long.
Yes, sir?
I got you something.
We went around
Chinatown earlier,
- and I thought of you.
- Here.
- Hmm.
- Moon cake.
I hope you like it.
Oh, sir, I'm sorry.
I'm actually allergic to them.
On moon cakes?!
No, they're actually
my favorite!
I'm actually allergic
to corny jokes.
Hmm.
Alright, sir.
Wait a minute.
I'm just trying
to be kind, Jacinto.
How is General Jacinto
doing, by the way?
My dad?!
He's alright, sir.
He's disappointed in you.
Because you failed
to do the demolition.
That's why I think we should
focus on our job, sir.
Goodbye, sir.
Wait.
Take this, please.
[PLASTIC RUSTLING]
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
[MAX] Enjoy.
Thank you, sir.
These are my favorite.
Thank you!
Your favorite?
That's my favorite too.
[CHUCKLING SOFTLY]
Sir.
You've been trying
to win her over for so long,
but you're always
getting rejected.
Why on earth
did you choose to pursue
the General's daughter?
You know what,
Santos,
she isn't just beautiful.
Max is also wealthy
and intelligent.
And her father
is also the General.
If I manage to win her over,
my reputation across the entire
police force will improve.
- Do you understand?
- [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
So don't worry, Santos.
I'll win her over eventually.
[DOOR CLICKS]
[DOOR CLOSES, CLICKS]
- [DOOR CLOSES]
- Ma'am.
Umali certainly has
a lot of nerve, doesn't he?
When will he give up?
I don't know, he's disgusting.
He thinks he's so handsome.
Does he think he can win me over
just because he's the Captain?
No way!
But, ma'am...
Your father's reputation
scares people.
He was silent once
you mentioned the General.
If you only knew. He's also
incredibly strict with us
It's like we're still
in the academy.
There's nothing we can do.
His word is always final.
I suppose you dream of becoming
a general, too, ma'am?
- Me?
- Mm-hmm.
No.
That's his dream
for his only son.
Oh!
So, you have a brother, ma'am?
Is he also a police?
Estrella,
that ballistic report...
[SIGHS] I might forget about it.
- Oh, alright.
- Yes.
Thank you for this, ma'am.
- [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
- Hope you'll like it.
[CHUCKLES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOOR CREAKS OPEN, CLOSES]
Later,
it's Chinese New Year time.
There's going to be
a lot of people.
That's why...
I want to earn
a lot of money.
- Do you understand?
- [MAN] You can count on us.
Don't ever come back here
unless you have the money.
- Yes, boss.
- Alright. Go!
[MAN] Let's go.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [MAN] Everyone, watch.
- How is it here?
[VON] Django. The news is out
that Gabo has taken in
Binoy, Tolits, and Daboy.
They're now part of his group!
What?
Those idiots!
They just heard that
I got outsmarted by Gabo,
and they betrayed me!
Gabo is building up his forces.
He's recruiting people
to go up against me.
[ROMY] It won't be long before
they start acting
like they own the place.
That's not going to happen.
I've known for a long time
that Gabo wants
to rule over Ginintuang Lupa.
But I won't let that happen.
As long as I'm alive,
this is our place!
[PAQUITO] Django.
Before Gabo gets the chance
to gain more influence,
you should cut his horns
while it's early.
We're going to build up
our forces, Pa.
I'll make sure...
that Gabo won't be able
to make a move.
Continue training!
- You three are next!
- [MAN] Go ahead.
Let's go.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[GONG CLANGING]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[VAN DOOR SLIDING OPEN]
We'll scout the area.
Sharpen your eyes.
We need to see Mr. Chan.
He'll bring us to Tiger.
[KAREN] Are you sure
Mr. Chan is there?
Can't we move closer
so we can get a better look
at the place?
Alright, listen.
Bullet! Borromeo.
Look around inside.
Find out if Mr. Chan
is there, okay?
- Yes, sir.
- Let's go.
[GONG CLANGING]
How will we know if the person
we're looking for is here?
- Oh, I don't know.
- Well, that's easy!
Let's rob this place,
and ask where Mr. Chan is.
- Ow! Ouch! You jerk!
- What's with you?
- Rob it on your own.
- That's not our job.
Our job is to find out
who owns that.
Shh! What's with you?
Shut up, you're too noisy!
Someone might overhear that
we're looking for Mr. Chan.
It'd be better to wait for Gabo.
How are we going
to wait for Gabo
when his father's
in the hospital?
We might miss the man
he's looking for.
We were given
a picture, remember?
You're still complaining?
Are you still coming with us?
Yeah, we're joining you!
We'll do whatever you want.
What do you want to do?
Want to eat first?
Let's eat first.
- We have a job to do, remember?
- Alright, we're not eating.
[GONG CLANGING]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Uh, miss?
Hello!
Miss, how much
do these cost nowadays?
[STAFF] The 18-carat necklace
is around 8000 pesos.
That's a bit high.
Could you...
...maybe cheapen it?
If we buy a lot,
could you give us a discount?
Only my boss can decide on that.
- Is your boss here?
- Yes, he is.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
What if we split
into two groups?
So we don't look sketchy.
The three of you can go
somewhere far,
so I won't be able to smell you.
Then let's come up
with our own gimmick,
so we don't look stupid
waiting here.
No, let's do it this way.
Let's split into two groups
to avoid suspicion.
Let's stay on the other side.
[TEKLA] You just repeated
what I said!
- This jerk...
- You're such a jerk.
- You just changed her tone.
- Go!
- Come on, come on!
- Survey properly!
Alright, miss, how about...
We'll look around,
and just come back
- if we don't see anything else.
- Okay, I'll wait here.
- Thank you.
[BINOY] Where will we look
for them when we're separated?
Let it go and just follow.
Tekla's already mad.
You know she stabs people
when she's mad.
- Ow! Ow, ouch!
- Hey! Hey.
- Are you blind?!
- Me, blind?
You didn't see me
when I'm this big?
Wow, this guy's ballsy!
What do you want?
What do you want, huh?
[JAMES] You think you're tough?
Do we look like small fish
to you?
[BINOY] Ah! Don't you know
who we are?
You want your blood
to trickle down?
I'll put this in your head!
- I'll put it inside!
- Let's leave, Bullet.
They'll only destroy
our mission.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- They're approaching!
- Here I go!
I almost had you.
Good thing you walked away.
You know, if they didn't leave,
and I couldn't hold back,
- I'll do this to them!
- The other guy's useless!
His body's so big,
he's on asteroids!
- What's "asteroid"?
- The one gym people
- inject in their arms.
- Oh, yeah!
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sam, positive.
- Mr. Chan's inside.
- How can you be sure?
We pretended to buy,
and asked for a discount.
The staff said she had
to ask her boss about it.
[BULLET] We didn't stay long.
She might get suspicious.
Alright. Let's wait here.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Sir Victor!
- Mr. Wang, how are you?
I'm great, I'm great.
- How are you?
- Business is doing good.
- [VICTOR] Good, good. Great.
- [WANG] Yes, yes.
- Good to see you.
- Thank you. See you, see you!
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MONEY RUSTLING]
- [CHAN] Is that ready?
- [WOMAN] Yes, Mr. Chan.
- 200 million pesos.
- Okay, good.
[PHONE RINGING]
- Hello?
- Victor!
Your money is ready.
I'm sorry, Mr. Chan,
but I will be late.
I have a wedding to attend.
But, after this,
I'll go to the bar.
[CHAN] Okay, no problem!
My place is very near bar.
Anytime, I can go.
See you, then.
[LINE DROPS]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- What can we even do here?
- We need a side job, right?
We could dance or sing.
We could even rap!
Anything to earn money.
You know the drill.
Drop a coin, distract,
and steal.
- Hey.
- Hey, you know,
I'm going to tell
on you to Gabo.
Hey, I was just kidding.
- "Just kidding?"
- Let's find a spot to sing at.
What about here?
[GUITAR STRUMMING]
Hey, Mister!
May we borrow your guitar?
I'll give you 50 pesos so
you can buy some food.
Sure, there's not a lot of
generous people today.
Well, that works for us.
[IPE] Here's 50 pesos.
You jerk!
This is just 20 pesos.
You're tricking me!
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Why, this jerk!
You're not blind!
That's none of your business!
You do what earns you money!
Just take care of my guitar.
If you break this,
I'll be looking for you three.
- Okay, fine!
- All right.
Hand it over.
I'll borrow this too, okay?
Take care of that!
We'd miss out if
we just stayed here.
It's Chinese New Year.
- We can earn a lot of money.
- Right!
We could've taken a gig.
So what are we waiting for?
Let's leave for now.
There's a lot of people handing
out red envelopes in Chinatown.
What if Gabo looks for us?
He'll punish us for sure.
He won't look for us.
That's not going to happen.
If he'll come here,
he'll call us first.
[TOLITS] Right?
Let's get going.
Let's not waste time.
[BONG AND IPE] One, two,
three, four!
[SINGING] Every Filipino
Sing with us
Happy Chinese New Year
Every Filipino-Chinese
Sing with us
Happy Chinese New Year
Have a prosperous new year
What a timely celebration
Make sure to use every
opportunity wisely
Especially because the sleeping
dragons have awakened
[TRADITIONAL CHINESE
MUSIC PLAYING]
Dances and drums making noise
Sticky rice cakes
They're giving away
[TRADITIONAL CHINESE
MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TOLITS] Hey! Why are you there?
We shouldn't go there!
You should go here
at the right side!
You're just looking at
the girls there!
Ouch! Ouch! Hey!
[RAPPING]
Happy Chinese New Year!
Come on, everybody!
Kung Hei Fat Choi!
Bro, these guys are good.
Yeah. They sound
like real rappers.
[BULLET CHUCKLES]
Ignore them.
Stay focused on the target.
We can't let them slip away.
Copy, Captain.
[RAPPING]
Sometimes life's so hard,
you don't even know
how real change
can ever happen.
[FARTS]
Damn, that stinks!
Who farted?
Daboy, give us a warning
next time!
That wasn't me!
[RETCHES]
The smell's sticking
to my clothes!
- [TOLITS] Hey, wait!
- [RETCHES]
[RETCHES]
[WOMAN] Hey, what the hell?
Don't stay there!
We're working here.
Get inside!
Kung Hei Fat Choi!
[TEKLA SINGING]
Limbaga, Borromeo, and I
are changing positions.
All right. Be careful.
We're on a mission,
and you're still flirting.
Let's go.
Come on, everybody!
Kung Hei Fat Choi!
[TEKLA] Let's hear it!
- Give us a round of applause!
- [APPLAUSE]
- [BONG] We're exhausted!
- [TEKLA] Yeah.
[IPE] That's it!
[BONG] If anyone else
wants to chip in...
Kung Hei Fat Choi!
[CROWD CHEERING]
[IPE] For those who haven't
donated yet!
[CROWD CHEERING]
We worked hard for this!
Show us some love!
- [GABO] Hey!
- [BONG] Gabo!
Any news?
Oh.
Well?
Have you found him?
Not yet.
We even posed as rappers
so we wouldn't look suspicious.
Maybe we'll spot someone
keeping watch around here.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [CROWD CHEERING]
- [DRUMS AND CYMBALS PLAYING]
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Are you sure
this will work, ma'am?
Everything is at stake here.
This will work.
Mr. Chan will lead us
to Tiger.
We just need to find them
and catch them in the act.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[BONG] This was a nice gig,
Gabo.
We made a lot of money.
Let's not look for
Mr. Chan anymore.
Maybe we can make
enough here
to cover your father's
hospital bills.
No.
We need to catch Tiger.
We're going to follow Mr. Chan
because he'll lead us to Tiger.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
In times of need...
I don't believe
Gabo will help us!
I will figure this out.
What are you going to do?
She's applying for a job.
Help her out.
Have you forgotten
what your family has done to us?
You've got some nerve
coming here asking for a favor.
Rudy really needs our help.
Alright. You need help
with his funeral?
With his treatment!
I hired Betchay so I could
use her against Gabo.
Courage is needed.
I'm going in to see
if Mr. Chan's there.
Tekla, find out if
Mr. Chan's inside.
- Oh, that's beautiful.
- Excuse me.
That item's reserved already.
Oh? I don't see
anyone's name on it.
You may be tall,
but I can take you on!
Mr. Chan!
They're causing trouble!
I have a meeting
at Jade Imperial.
I know that place!
It's a popular bar nearby!
The target's on the move.
Target in sight.
We'll follow him.
Let's meet there! Move!
We need to catch Tiger.